[
    {
      "question": "Which of these color contrast ratios defines the minimum WCAG 2.1 Level AA requirement for normal text?",
      "options": ["4.5 : 1", "3 : 1", "2.5 : 1", "5 : 1"],
      "answer": "4.5 : 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the acronym WCAG stand for?",
      "options": [
        "Web Content Accessibility Guidelines",
        "Web Community Accessible Guidelines",
        "Web Compliance Accessibility Guidelines",
        "World Wide Compliance Access Guide"
      ],
      "answer": "Web Content Accessibility Guidelines"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which ARIA role should be used for an interactive button?",
      "options": ["role=\"banner\"", "role=\"button\"", "role=\"image\"", "role=\"link\""],
      "answer": "role=\"button\""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the minimum font size recommended by WCAG for body text?",
      "options": ["10px", "12px", "14px", "16px"],
      "answer": "16px"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does ARIA stand for?",
      "options": [
        "Accessible Rich Internet Applications",
        "Advanced Rich Internet Applications",
        "Asynchronous Rich Internet Applications",
        "Authorized Rich Internet Applications"
      ],
      "answer": "Accessible Rich Internet Applications"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which HTML attribute is used to describe the purpose of an image for visually impaired users?",
      "options": ["title", "alt", "longdesc", "src"],
      "answer": "alt"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which WCAG principle ensures that contents are distinguishable and understandable?",
      "options": ["Perceivable", "Operable", "Understandable", "Robust"],
      "answer": "Understandable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following attributes is used to provide a text equivalent for non-text content in HTML?",
      "options": ["role", "aria-label", "alt", "title"],
      "answer": "alt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these input types helps to ensure the correct format for email entries?",
        "options": ["<input type=\"url\">", "<input type=\"email\">", "<input type=\"text\">", "<input type=\"submit\">"],
        "answer": "<input type=\"email\">"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ARIA attribute is used to announce dynamic changes in content to screen readers?",
        "options": ["aria-live", "aria-atomic", "aria-disabled", "aria-expanded"],
        "answer": "aria-live"
    }
]  